All right.
(Sheldon(picks up train):)Let's see.
"Bernie Bunny Has Two Daddies Now."
That's probably
about homosexual rabbits.
"Gerry the Gerbil
and the Bullies on the Bus."
(Sheldon(picks up train):)Read it, not helpful.
Ooh. Well, here we go.
"Stu the Cockatoo is New at the Zoo."
"Author Sarah Carpenter...
(Sheldon(picks up train):)...lives in Fort Wayne, Indiana...
(Sheldon(picks up train):)...with her husband
and best friend, Mark...
...and their cockatoo, Stu."
(Sheldon(picks up train):)Hardly makes her an expert
in making friends, wouldn't you agree?
(Little girl:)I don't like birds. They scare me.
(Sheldon:)Me too.
(Sheldon:)Most people don't see it.
(Sheldon:)What are you reading?
(Girl:)Curious George.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I do like monkeys.